The paper identifies its dataset as the Center for Research and Security Prices,
论文指出他们使用的数据集是“Center for Research in Security Prices”
which is often abbreviated as CRSP and can be referred to as CRISP.
经常简称 CRSP 读作 crisp
This is a fairly well-known pricing dataset.
这是一个有名的股价数据集
And if you check out their website,
从官网可以了解到
you can see that the data is available via subscription.
他们的数据需要订阅才能访问
We don't use that data precisely,
我们并不使用该数据集
but we are using a pricing dataset which is very similar.
但是用到的股价数据集比较相似
It's also helpful to check what stock universe
还需要查看作者认为
the authors think are most relevant to the factors they are analyzing.
与他们分析的因子最相关的股票池
Even though a factor would ideally be applicable and useful for a broad range of stocks,
虽然因子理想情况下适用于更广泛的股票
it's also possible that certain factors only generate
但是有可能某些因子
meaningful signals for a certain subgroup of stocks.
仅对特定的股票子集能生成有意义的信号
In the abstract, the authors mentioned that mean
在摘要部分 作者提到
reversion or momentum factors that they're
他们评估的均值回归或动量因子
evaluating are more pronounced for hard to value firms.
更适用于“harder to value firms”（难以评估的企业）
If we look through the paper for mention of harder to value firms,
我们在论文中查询“harder to value firms”一词
we see how they define them in section four titled,
发现他们在第四部分进行了定义
Short-term Overnight Return Persistence,
标题为“Short-term Overnight Return Persistence,
Hard to Value Firms and Institutional Share Holdings.
Hard to Value Firms and Institutional Share Holdings.”
According to other papers they cite,
根据他们引用的其他论文
harder to value firms are more volatile,
难以评估的企业波动性更大
have a smaller market cap,
属于小盘股 新企业
are newer companies, currently less profitable,
目前盈利不高
and considered high growth companies as exhibited by higher price to earnings ratios.
并且属于高增长公司 因为市盈率较高
Remember that I said when you see and, think conditional factor.
之前我提到 当你看到“AND”一词时 想想条件因子
If you wanted to implement these specific ideas,
如果你想实施这些观点
you would do so via the mechanics of a conditional factor.
需要用到条件因子
We don't do that in this exercise however.
但是在这道练习中我们不会采用条件因子
The authors provide some context for why harder to value firms may be more likely to
作者解释了为何难以评估的企业更有可能
exhibit overbuying at market open or weekly momentum of closed open returns.
在开盘时或收盘到开盘收益率每周动量中呈现炒高信号
The hypothesis is that individual investors may rely more
假说指出 当公司的基本面难以衡量时
on sentiment when the fundamentals of the company are more difficult to measure.
散户更依赖于对公司的正面/负面情绪
This sentiment is expressed in the recent closed open returns of the stock.
这种情绪用最近的收盘到开盘收益率表示
We can also scan the paper for useful methodology,
我们还可以看看论文是否提出了适用范围更广的方法
which we can apply more broadly to any factors that we're evaluating.
从而让我们可以将这些方法应用到任意需要评估的因子上
For instance, in section two,
例如 在第二部分
the authors define the weekly overnight return on the stock.
作者定义了每周隔夜收益率
If you haven't read this section yet,
如果你没读到这部分的话
you may imagine taking a window of five days daily returns,
可能会想到查看五天的每日收益率
adding them up to get the weekly cumulative close to open return.
将它们相加得出每周累积收盘到开盘收益率
The authors do something slightly different.
作者的方法有所不同
They take the average of the daily returns over five trading days,
他们计算了五个交易日的每日收益率平均值
then they multiply by five.
然后乘以五
Can you think of how this is different or why they may do this?
你知道这样做有何区别或者为何要这样做吗？
Notice that if we had missing data,
如果我们缺少数据
then simply adding up the daily closed open returns over a five-day window,
那么将五天的每日收盘到开盘收益率相加
may not make each week comparable.
那不同周的数据就不好比较了
If a certain week is missing data for one day,
如果有一周的某一天缺少数据了
then we would only have four days worth of returns to add up.
那么只能将四天的收益率相加
By taking the daily average and then multiplying by five,
计算每日平均收益率并乘以五
we can better deal with missing data and help make
可以更好地处理缺少数据的情形
each week's cumulative return more comparable to other weeks.
使每周的累积收益率与其他周的更对等